The application by far, Chief of the Third Amendment.
Heavenly Father, we're thankful for you and we're thankful we could be here tonight.
Do the business of the community.
Lord, we're just thankful for council members who are willing to serve and just give us wisdom and guidance as they do their business tonight.
Keeps all safe as we head home to your name we pray.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America and to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation, under God, indivisible with liberty and justice for all.
Lord, we'll begin by giving personal verses.
Bibleist.
I'm going to have a couple of questions.
So, and forgive me if it's this is the wrong meeting.
It's always confusing.
Under the purchased orders for the airport,
there's something from Arthur Gallagher for $26,000.
I bet that they're insurance.
It's under risk management.
It's an insurance for the.
Okay.
I've just, I've never seen something that large on there.
Thought I'd ask about it.
Yeah.
Just where you'll see that.
Gotcha.
And there was one more.
So back to the airport.
The construction administration for.
One for nineteen three forty eight more for ten thousand ninety five.
Yep.
What is.
Okay.
And then we still manage to stay in budget.
Perfect.
And now we'll make a motion to approve.
Say.
He said.
Hi.
Don't go.
Joe's.
Marker.
Six clients for bands.
All group.
Don't ship group.
Say it.
He said.
Hi.
Don't go.
I.
Marker.
I'm staying.
Seven minutes in the August.
Nineteep.
Twenty twenty five ringer meeting.
I'll just twenty six.
Twenty five ringer meeting.
Motion to approve.
Second.
So.
Right.
He said.
So.
Marker.
Hey.
The clear.
The list.
I miss you.
An equipment.
Including in the packet.
As a surplus.
And authorized.
I was.
The option.
So this.
Tonight.
Party.
I know.
Signing authority for the trust manager or his counsel needs.
Good evening.
So what we're working on.
MUSIC.
We had, I believe it was a couple of months ago where we brought the surplus list to y'all.
We're working on that. We have a date now of September 27th, where we will be helping the auction.
And so these are just more items that we want to add to that surplus list.
Jones, type burns.
He's the so-called Parker.
Hi.
Do you business?
Any of which have risen since the posting of this agenda?
May we have one thing, Mr. Now, when I'm bringing up.
So we had a meeting scheduled today with the St. James Court.
So this is something that's been from a prior administration.
So they have a bill that's been solely like paying it off or working to pay off.
And so they did not show up today.
So we made the decision that we were going to notify all the tenants that we're going to show off their power in 30 days if they did not pay.
Okay.
Mrs. Good with it.
We have to look the tenants now in case someone's on live preserving,
be like oxygen or something like that.
So we have to give them 30 days notice so that they can make out their rates.
That's before we shut utilities.
And then after that 30 days, we can shut them all.
How large.
We would say hello.
Six.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Why did it go so long?
I have been on a $14,000 a month.
And I'm paying.
How long is this $14,000 payment plan going to go on?
That's what we're trying to meet with them.
So why was that even allowed?
And that was a prior administration where it's trying to fix it.
Well, that's kind of ridiculous.
How much was there monthly bill?
About 30.
It fluctuates between you and half a bill.
Yeah, there's something to go anywhere from 7,000 to 30.
You know, you have to think of fall and winter.
So.
How many tenants are there?
Are you nuts?
That way, y'all.
That way, don't know.
That's a civil issue between the clients and the owner of that building.
So they can take care of that on their own.
All right.
They have their own potential causes of action.
I guess they're limo or who is contracted with them for a.
This is your rent.
And your utilities are included.
And then not taking care of the utilities.
But legally, we have to let them know before we shut off utilities.
Just in case someone is also.
So, you know.
I don't know.
But legally, we have to let them know before we shut off utilities.
Just in case someone is also.
And we want to realize this was previous administration.
The six figures this long is ridiculous.
That shouldn't ever happen.
Those best ones get in part in the part of the behind each month.
Yeah.
So they've only been required to pay.
Partial payment of their current bill.
No, so they're just.
According to.
We had, they were just paying a certain amount every month, no matter if the bill was above this or below this.
So we talked to Matt, what a few months ago, and then we've been trying to make contact with him.
And so obviously we know it will be in the news.
We assume so we want to make the board aware.
And we're trying to rectify the issue.
We sent a certified letter of all this.
That was our receipt that back today.
And it's just common practice for the billing office to raise the like that.
If it is, as your legal counsel, I'm advising you that you need to change that.
That is not.
If that is policy, I don't think it is.
But if so, my responsibility is the five of you.
And that can't be happening with city money.
Well, if it's a...
Or if it's a...
Just tell me.
A house.
How long do we give them?
I don't know.
10 days.
So why have we left this go so far?
Six figures.
That's a bunch of money people.
Yeah, that's our turn to fix it.
Commercial accounts go longer.
I mean, that is something that they've always done.
How old is this thing going?
Since 23.
As far back as I have.
I mean, I'm sure it's been before then.
Well, the tenants we were receiving a notice.
Yes.
We're going to put it on their door.
Yeah.
And you have to think as the bill gets larger, you know,
our late fees...
I mean, it compounds very quickly, you know.
So...
Do we have anyone else that's on something like this?
That we're...
We just want to make you aware because without a few of them I reach out and say,
Hey, they're going to...
Do you want to get some of them all?
Yeah.
Do we need to change that?
Do we need to do something with that kind of a deal to where we don't let something get it way out of hand?
Well, we are working on...
We need to do something.
Well, we're working on a policy.
Yeah.
There's not...
The policy that they've been working off of is a red line version.
So we are working on creating a utility-building policy.
And my idea is that the council should approve that policy because you are responsible for their money.
And the board, I'm sorry.
I keep getting my meetings mixed up.
And just so they must say, MSU A board is a way where we do have some large commercial customers that don't pay their bills on time.
And I mean, but they pay every month.
They just don't pay them.
Something.
Yeah.
But I know.
I know.
Yes.
I'm just making you aware that I know that's all.
Maybe a little wider.
We not kick.
Shut them off in 10 days too.
My company is one of those companies because the billing has to go overseas to get up here
They pay pay down
Yeah, sure
This is six years
This is the money the shitty can use and the situation is the reason that it is gotten this way is because they have one of those
What a small pond what I call a chill on time of the building and yet evaporates water at
Just a ridiculous right in this heat and humidity. So it's just been
They've just not replaced it or fixed that issue and they allow it to get this way
But I mean if you can pay half of your bail
Why would you fix it?
So it's making the order where they were back to five of the issue then and he didn't even accept his
Letter of the juicy
Well, he's not even willing to work with us. It don't seem like we had a meeting so today
Send them back try to head to the version and they said we don't want that or
They'll leave a card on your door and the property manager
I have talked to her in tech today and she did know that it was at the post office because she sent me the notice that they sent her
And she just didn't go so the owner knows there
You come off as disrespectful. I just when we start talking about the the board or the council handle and money
Public money. I get really serious because that's like my whole job is to
Well, this was I'm going to come forward, but I agree but I would have liked to have been made aware
So we're trying to fix the issue and obviously we're at the next
To fix the issue and so we're going to
Because if it was my house has already been turned off or any other Joe smoke out here and have been gone and been turned off
This is uncool for something has to happen. Somebody else might not about this
Before I got myself in a situation words
30 days to pay and then what they're shut up show off is that my whole in full. That's what I'm wondering. No further negotiations
Contrary or we love and anything contractually that's going to
It was just a car and another.
Yeah.
It's just been happened.
They bought it?
They don't know that.
So it's the month they bought it.
It's been happened.
I mean, how many months did they have that killer issue?
Which you try to work with them all?
If they've been, if you've lost evidence in that.
So I'm sure you've fixed the killer for other six fingers or that.
But if you fixed the killer, then you might not have to pay your whole bill,
which was approximately that time's twice what you're having to pay.
I'm sorry.
I don't really go to the side for the left or here at all.
So you wrote.
They're watching the pay your bill.
I don't go to the side for you.
Everybody else is flipping bills.
Well, if he's already got this.
That's not much money in debt to us.
Does he have a tax lien?
We'd follow, you know.
If we follow the lien, the plan is to do a lien for closure and on the front end
and not let it get to a situation where we take a chance
on the county court, not collecting.
That's why we've been leaving that process.
That's the plan is to follow a lien for closure on the front end.
So if I had shown up to the meeting today, I think Tyler had in mind,
like $50,000,000.
Plus, they're current bill.
And we're just going to email the board and say,
this is a agreement.
Because we can do a payment plan.
So we're working with people and say, pay this much.
Plus, you're current bill.
And if you don't do it, then we're going to shut your power off.
And we can kind of, you know, say, we've notified everybody.
I don't know the idea of what they didn't show up.
And they didn't answer the call.
I don't know.
I think we're like, you know, Matt hasn't been in that role for a whole long time.
So I think he's doing a good job of finding these things.
I'm like, you know, bringing them up.
I'm bringing to our attention to fix.
I mean, is that fair to say, Kevin?
I just wanted to kind of clarify.
Because I know that you said you didn't say, well, how did I go on this long?
Well, everybody's just now learning about it.
And it's new to everybody.
Yeah.
I mean, I think that we're taking the right steps as far as trying
to get fixed.
I mean, I think I mean, I had to say this sort of board, but we're
clean up a lot of stuff.
I mean, as a fair to say, when we updated the rates, I know Molly and Matt and
all the utility building staff went through and like some people were
maybe in a different rate class, and they should have been there
whatever you know, which I mean, Matt is new down there.
You know, those people are new.
So it's like, one of the things we didn't want to change our rates is to make sure
these people are in the proper rate category.
So I mean, we're working hard.
Obviously when you work hard to fix stuff, stuff like this comes up.
So that's my frustration with you guys.
Right.
Mind what you're being taken advantage of by this landlord.
Yeah.
I think we're all frustrated.
It's just this, it's a lot of money.
No need to get fixed.
It's a lot of money.
And the main thing is he's taking my advice. He's still collecting his breath from his tents and if he didn't collect that rent, they're out
Yeah, so I'm a lot of this being a different. He should understand this completely
I guess that's from our heart that I just
Sculptate. We're seeing
The tent is on the way to the third bill. It's the end of like that's
I'm tired of that
Yeah, when the tents find their rent
Their bills are included, so they're similar and they're dealers are getting paid
Yeah
One of those tenants is a lawyer that some maybe don't have them more of a thoughts and put a button
Everybody's here that they do have a machine. I'm so I've never shoot a gun to that
Every Trent there's like
Yeah
I'm just doing the math
So
It's a very simple
There's a couple of months that they know his life. There's so much of their bills
All right, just because you know you have to be like the bill and the late charge
So I just making them aware there's a few months that their light fee is almost as much as their bill if that makes sense
You know
So when you're supposed to their usage in electric or water all of it all of it
Yeah, I'll see what I'll say in his like for that
I mean, I don't know how far back I think it was, but like 20 times I thought this was like
How did you like it any year?
And that's a little bit better
I'm going to get light fees
I'm going to say I'm going to say I'm going to get light fees
I mean
Look I'm not going to jump though
It's engineering
Well thanks for having us so good
Sorry to be the very bad news
We just want to make the board aware because I mean as we crack down us I mean it's like this
I'm sure that some detint it's kind of called the news and then the news is going to reach out you know
Let's know we can help fight for them.
Me and our name.
Yes, sir.
We just want to make you aware.
Testing.
Do you do the alphabets?
I don't know.
Anybody want to follow up after that?
Oh, yeah, let's go anyway.
Not that one.
There it is.
You want to go right there.
Stay.
Okay.
Well, I haven't trust me in your communications.
No.
12 adjournment.
Check.
So cool.
Hi.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you.